http://www.sarasotacrew.org/privacy-policy

Our CoachesOur StaffContact UsLogin
Crew Facts
Guide to College Recruit...
Who We AreOur MissionOur Impact
Crew FactsCollege ScholarshipsTuition Assistance & ScholarshipGuide to College RecruitingCrew Graduating ClassesAlumni
202020192018201720162015201420132012201120102009200820072006200520042003Our CoachesBoard of Directors Our StaffOur FleetParent OrganizationFinancials/StewardshipPrograms
Youth Rowing
High SchoolMiddle SchoolElementary SchoolAdultsAbout UsAdult MembershipsPractice ScheduleAdult Open Rows/SocialsLearn to Row ClassesAdaptive/Para RowingCamps
Pre-Elite Training CampSummer Camps and ClinicsTeam BuildingCOVID - 19 ProceduresSupport Us
Giving TuesdayCapital Campaign
Case for SupportGround BreakingFirst RowDonateDonateGeneral FundScholarship FundEquipment FundWays of GivingDonate onlineMail or PhoneMatching ContributionsGifts in KindCompanies & FoundationsEventsNon Regatta EventsNon Regatta EventsAdult Open Rows/SocialsLearn to Row ClassesEvents CalendarPress ReleasesJoin UsYouth Rowing
High SchoolMiddle SchoolElementary SchoolAdult Rowing
Adult RowingLearn to Row Alumni Rowing
AlumniPre-Elite/U23 Rowing
Pre-Elite/U23Camps and ClinicsParents
High School ParentsMiddle School ParentsElementary School ParentsVolunteer Opportunities/Sign UpAlumniBoat StorageRowing 101
About RowingGlossaryRowing Links
2016 Rules of Rowing2016 Wiki Rowing OverviewRegatta CentralUS RowingWorld RowingWaivers
NOARA WaiverMedia
ImagesDocumentsPress ReleasesFall 2017Halloween Regatta 2017National Signing Day 11.2017Plant Invite-Fall Sprints 2017Fall 2018Masters World RegattaHalloween Regatta 2018Plant Invite - Fall Sprints 2018Fall 20192019 World Rowing Championships2019 Gold at World2019 Groundbreaking Ceremony2019 Head of the HogNational Signing Day - 11.13.19Spring 2017Novice Regatta American Youth Cup IOARS InvitationalAmerican Youth Cup IIFlorida West District ChampionshipsFlorida Sculling State ChampionshipsFlorida Sweep State Championships Southeast Regional ChampionshipsSpring 2018Plant Sprints-Spring Sprints #1Plant Sprints-Spring Sprints #2National Signing Day 02.18OARS Invitational Tampa Mayor's Cup American Youth Cup IIFSRA West District ChampionshipsSculling State ChampionshipsSweep State ChampionshipsFlorida Masters RegattaSpring 2019American Youth Cup IPlant Invite Spring Sprints #1OARS Tampa Mayor's CupSculling StatesWorld StageHalifax RegattaSpring 2020National Signing Day - 2.5.2020American Youth Cup I OARS Youth InvitationalOARS Masters InvitationalPlant Invite - Spring Sprints #2Login
You will need to register in one of the programs before you can log in.
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Print
Email
Privacy Policy for Sarasota Crew, Inc
At https://SarasotaCrew.org, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors, and we recognize the need to provide additional privacy protection for children on the Sarasota Crew website.  Our privacy policies are guided by the United State’s Children’s Online Protection Act of 1998, as well as data privacy laws in the United States and other applicable counties.  Younger visitors should always check with their parents or guardians before entering information on any website.  This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by https://SarasotaCrew.org and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Types of Information We Collect
We collect:
Registration information you provide when you create an account, such as your first name and surname, country of residence, gender, date of birth, email address, username, and password;
Transaction information you provide when you request information, or purchase a product or service from us, such as your postal address, telephone number, and payment information;
Information sent either one-to-one or within a limited group using our message, or similar functionality, where we are permitted by applicable law to collect this information;
Information we obtain from a third party, such as a site or platform provider, about use of our applications on third-party platforms or devices;
Location information, including location information provided by a mobile or other device interacting with our sites, or associated with your IP address, where we are permitted by law to process this information;
Activity information about your use, and the use by any person(s) you authorize through your account, of our sites and applications, such as the content you view or post, how often you use our services, and your preferences; and
Usage, viewing, technical, and device data when you visit our sites, use our applications on third-party sites or platforms, or open emails we send, including your browser or device type, unique device identifier, and IP address.
How We Collect Your Information
We collect the information you provide to us when you request or purchase products, services, or information from us, register with us, participate in public forums or other activities on our sites and applications, respond to guest surveys, or otherwise interact with us using one or more devices.  You may provide information in a variety of ways, including by typing or using voice commands.
Like any other website, https://SarasotaCrew.org uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Sharing Your Information with Other Entities
We will not share your personal information with a third party outside of Sarasota Crew, Inc except in limited circumstances, including:
When you allow us to share your personal information with another company, such as:
Electing to share your personal information with carefully selected companies
Directing us to share your personal information with third-party sites
Responding to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims or government inquiries or to protect the rights of members or the public
Please note that once we share your personal information with another company, the information received by the other company is controlled by that company and becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
Your Controls and Choices
Correcting, updating, and deleting your registration account (Logout);
Choosing or changing your choices for subscriptions, newsletters, and alerts;
Choosing whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to you;
Choosing not to provide additional information
Log Files
https://SarasotaCrew.org follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Our Advertising Partners
Some of the advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners include:
Google
Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their website. For easier access, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of https://SarasotaCrew.org.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on https://SarasotaCrew.org, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that https://SarasotaCrew.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
https://SarasotaCrew.org’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here:
Privacy Policy Links.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in https://SarasotaCrew.org. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://SarasotaCrew.org. By continuing to access or use this site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Types of Information We Collect
We collect:
Registration information you provide when you create an account, such as your first name and surname, country of residence, gender, date of birth, email address, username, and password;
Transaction information you provide when you request information, or purchase a product or service from us, such as your postal address, telephone number, and payment information;
Information sent either one-to-one or within a limited group using our message, or similar functionality, where we are permitted by applicable law to collect this information;
Information we obtain from a third party, such as a site or platform provider, about use of our applications on third-party platforms or devices;
Location information, including location information provided by a mobile or other device interacting with our sites, or associated with your IP address, where we are permitted by law to process this information;
Activity information about your use, and the use by any person(s) you authorize through your account, of our sites and applications, such as the content you view or post, how often you use our services, and your preferences; and
Usage, viewing, technical, and device data when you visit our sites, use our applications on third-party sites or platforms, or open emails we send, including your browser or device type, unique device identifier, and IP address.
How We Collect Your Information
We collect information you provide to us when you request or purchase products, services, or information from us, register with us, participate in public forums or other activities on our sites and applications, respond to guest surveys, or otherwise interact with us using one or more devices.  You may provide information in a variety of ways, including by typing or using voice commands.
Like any other website, https://SarasotaCrew.org uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.
Sharing Your Information with Other Entities
We will not share your personal information with a third party outside of Sarasota Crew, Inc except in limited circumstances, including:
When you allow us to share your personal information with another company, such as:
Electing to share your personal information with carefully selected companies
Directing us to share your personal information with third-party sites
Responding to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims or government inquiries or to protect the rights of members or the public
Please note that once we share your personal information with another company, the information received by the other company is controlled by that company and becomes subject to the other company’s privacy practices.
Your Controls and Choices
Correcting, updating, and deleting your registration account (Logout);
Choosing or changing your choices for subscriptions, newsletters, and alerts;
Choosing whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to you;
Choosing not to provide additional information
Log Fileshttps://SarasotaCrew.org follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Our Advertising PartnersSome of the advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners include:
GoogleEach of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their website. For easier access, an updated and hyperlinked resource is maintained here:
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of https://SarasotaCrew.org.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on https://SarasotaCrew.org, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that https://SarasotaCrew.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
https://SarasotaCrew.org’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here:
Privacy Policy Links.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in https://SarasotaCrew.org. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://SarasotaCrew.org. By continuing to access or use this site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
Connect
343 Palmetto Ave, Osprey, FL, 34229
1 941 966 9791
teamAdmin@sarasotaCrew.org
Contact Us
Upcoming Events
DEC
06
Sarasota Crew Intrasquad Regatta Fall 2020 - High School Rowers
High School
Nathan Benderson Park
DEC
19
Sarasota Crew Intrasquad Regatta Fall 2020 - Middle School Rowers
Sarasota Crew Intrasquad Regatta Fall 2020 - Elementary School Rowers
